{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "lf it is the best thing to do, it cannot be done ___ soon.",
      "a": "enough",
      "b": "too",
      "c": "ever",
      "d": "much",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Too [+ adjective/adverb]: used with a negative to mean 'not very'",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lisa looks ___ than she really is.",
      "a": "much older",
      "b": "more older",
      "c": "more old",
      "d": "the older",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Much/far/ rather/a little/a bit/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj \n- Comparative: adj + er (short adj)/ more adj (long adj) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___, their research team is made up of 10 members.",
      "a": "Completely",
      "b": "Entirely",
      "c": "Wholely",
      "d": "Altogether",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Altogether: used to emphasize that something has been done completely or has finished completely",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The streets were flooded because it has rained ___ all day long.",
      "a": "deeply",
      "b": "heavily",
      "c": "strongly",
      "d": "thickly",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": ".\n- We often use \"heavy\" with \"rain\" to imply that rain falls hard",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The war broke ___ at dawn.",
      "a": "off",
      "b": "in",
      "c": "down",
      "d": "out",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Break out: if something unpleasant such as a fire, fight, or war breaks out, it starts to happen",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Let's go _________ upstairs.",
      "a": "below",
      "b": "to",
      "c": "x",
      "d": "up",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- We say go upstairs or come upstairs",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Haven't you finished preparing your presentation ___?",
      "a": "too",
      "b": "yet",
      "c": "still",
      "d": "also",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n-Yet: used in negative statements and questions to talk about whether something that was expected has happened",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Asia is ___ the largest continent in the world.",
      "a": "a little",
      "b": "by far",
      "c": "a great deal",
      "d": "far away",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- By far/far and away: used to say that something is much better, worse etc than anything else",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is _________ to travel by air than by water.",
      "a": "a lot more exciting",
      "b": "much more excited",
      "c": "a lot more excited than",
      "d": "much exciting",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": ".\n- Much/far/ rather/a little/a bit/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj\n- Comparative: adj + er (short adj)/ more adj (long adj)\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Beatrice is ___ afraid of being left alone.",
      "a": "much",
      "b": "very",
      "c": "such",
      "d": "more",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Be much of: a large amount of something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}